http://www.numberoneshowplates.co.uk/privacy.html

.Useful Information
Home»
Privacy
Privacy Statement
Last updated: 20-07-08
Privacy Policy Statement For casual visitors to our website, we do not collect any information regarding domains, email addresses, or any other personal details.
The information that we collect from our customers is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending an email to us via the contact page stating that you do not wish to receive any further communications from our company.
If you have supplied us with your postal address online, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products, services or upcoming events. Please provide us with your exact name and address if you do not wish to receive such mailings, send details via the contact page.
Persons who have supplied us with their telephone number online may receive calls from us with information regarding orders they have placed on–line. Please provide us with your correct phone number via the contact page if you do not wish to receive any such contact.
NumberOneShowPlates.co.uk has created this Privacy Statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of our customers. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our websites.
Automatically collected information
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and keep track of how many visitors our websites have had, what country they have come from and what browser version they use. At no time is your IP address used to help identify you.
IP addresses are unique numeric identifiers that are assigned to each computer browser accessing the Internet. An IP address, by itself, cannot identify you personally. However, when combined with other information provided by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), your IP address can be used to identify the computer originating a message.
Cookies
We use cookies to help maintain a consistent experience for our customers. Cookies are used throughout our site for the shopping basket facility as this enables us to keep track of the products in your shopping basket. At no time is any personal information stored within a cookie.
Visitors to our site can refuse cookies by turning them off in their browser please note this will result in online purchasing becoming inaccessible due to the shopping basket function relying on cookies.
Personal information
Our websites use an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitors' contact information such as email address and telephone numbers. Contact information from order forms are used to send order details and information to our customers from our company only. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. The information that you provide to us will not be shared or sold to any other company or individuals at any time.
Security
All Payments from this site are taken through Pay Pal. When you make a purchase “proceed to checkout” you will be taken to a secure server. At the bottom of the page you will see a small padlock that informs you that your information is encrypted and you are on a secure server (SSL). Also, in the address bar the URL should start with “https://”. This Pay Pal only uses the highest level of Internet Security. At no time will your information be in any danger of theft.Pay Pals privacy policy: https://www.paypal.com/uk/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/ua/policy_privacy-outside
Public forums
We do not have any forums, guest books or message boards on this site. Under no circumstances will information passed to NumberOneShowPlates.co.uk from online forms, postal order forms or from any other source be made public.
Advertisers
This site does not use third party ad companies to display advertisements on our site.
However we do have outside companies advertising in our resources section (link exchange pages) these companies may use cookies and other information gathering methods to target ads to visitors.
External Links
NumberOneShowPlates.co.uk contains links to other sites. NumberOneShowPlates.co.uk is not responsible for the privacy policies, privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Choice/Opt–Out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.
If you do not wish to be placed on our mailing list please contact us via our contact page with a request to be removed. This will be carried out without any hesitation.
Contacting the Web Site
If at any time you wish to contact us, please go to the contact page. Here you will be able to contact us via on–line form, telephone, or mailing address.
Need more information or assistance?
If you have any problems with your order, please don‘t hesitate to contact us .
Sitemaps:
Information:
More Useful Resources:
Private plates on leased vehicles
